Register of the Howard Palfrey Jones papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Howard Palfrey Jones papers
1930-1978
74019
Hoover Institution Archives
128 manuscript boxes, 3 card file boxes, 3 cubic foot boxes, 5 envelopes, 2 oversize boxes, 8 slide boxes, 2 motion picture film reels, 12 phonotape reels (63.0 linear feet)
Writings, correspondence, reports, research files, studies, and printed matter relating to public finance and post-war reconstruction in Germany, 1945-1951, and to American relations with Indonesia and other areas of East Asia. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Jones, Howard Palfrey, 1899-
Access
Collection open for research. Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1974, with an increment received in 1982.
Accruals
Biographical Note
1899 January Born, Chicago, Illinois
1921 B.Litt., Columbia University, New York
1923-1925 Manager and Editor, Evansville, Indiana Press
1925-1927 Instructor, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, Michigan
1927-1929 Editor-in-Chief, Nellis Newspaper Chain, Mt. Clemens, Michigan
1931-1939 Editor, National Municipal Review, New York
1931-1938 Executive Director, National Municipal League, New York
1934-1938 Director of Research, New York State Commission on Revision of Tax Laws, New York
1933-1939 Lecturer, Professor, Graduate School of Journalism, Columbia University, New York
1934-1935 Lecturer, Graduate School, New York University, New York Lecturer, New York Institute of Banking, New York
1938-1942 Civil Service Commissioner, New York State
1943 Deputy Comptroller, New York State
1943-1947 Major to Colonel, General Staff Corps, U.S. Army
1950-1951 Director, Berlin Element, U.S. High Commissioner for Germany, Berlin
1951-1954 Counsellor of Embassy and Chargé d'Affaires of American Embassy, Taipeh, Taiwan
1954-1955 Chief of Mission, U.S. Economic Aid Mission to Indonesia
1955-1958 Deputy Assistant Secretary of State for the Far East
1958-1965 United States Ambassador to Indonesia
1965-1968 Chancellor, East-West Center, University of Hawaii, Honolulu
1968-1973 Senior Research Fellow, Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace, Stanford, California
1969-1972 Trustee, Christian Science Publishing Society, Boston, Massachusetts
1971 Author, Indonesia: The Possible Dream
1973 September Died, Atherton, California
Scope and Content of Collection
Writings, correspondence, reports, research files, studies, and printed matter relating to public finance and post-war reconstruction in Germany, 1945-1951, and to American relations with Indonesia and other areas of East Asia.
Alternate Forms Available
Digital copies of select records also available at https://digitalcollections.hoover.org.
Soekarno, 1901-1970.; United States. Department of State.; Asia, Southeastern.; Audiotapes.; Communism--Indonesia.; Communism.; Diplomats--United States.; East Asia--Foreign relations--United States.; East Asia.; Economic assistance, American--Southeast Asia.; Germany--History--1945-1955.; Germany.; Indonesia--Foreign relations--United States.; Indonesia--History--1950-1966.; Indonesia.; Malaya.; Malaysia.; Moving-pictures.; Reconstruction (1939-1951)--Germany.; United States--Foreign relations--East Asia.; United States--Foreign relations--Indonesia.; United States--Foreign relations.
- Correspondence, 1934-1973 (Box 1-20)
  Scope and Contents note
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
  - General, 1956-1970 (Box 1)
  - Unidentified, 1949-1971
  - Abdulgani, Roeslan, 1958-1971
  - Abdurachim, Kaka, 1967
  - Abdurrachman, Oemi, 1968-1969
  - Abidin, Zainal, 1969
  - Adams, Cindy, 1965-1971
  - Adams, Joey, 1965-1968
  - Adamson, G. W., 1970
  - Adamson, Neil C., Jr., 1970
  - Adcock, Clarence L., 1964
  - Adiutomo, Thomas S., 1966
  - Adler, Mortimer, 1970
  - Admawiria, S. S., 1964
  - Affeld, William C., Jr., 1967
  - Agbayani, Adeudato J., 1965
  - Agung, Ide Anak, 1967-1971
  - Agus Sumantri mantik, 1966
  - Ahmed, Zahir, 1968-1969
  - Alexander and Baldwin, 1966-1967
  - Alexander, Paul J., 1966
  - Alexander, Vera, 1969
  - Alford, Harold D., 1965
  - Alicia Patterson Fund, 1967
  - Alisjahbana, S. Takdir, 1966
  - Allen, Donald S., 1964
  - Allen, George V., 1964
  - Allen, Raymond B., 1960-1967
  - Allerton, John G., 1967
  - Allison, John M., 1965-1971
  - Allman, William, 1964-1965
  - Almosudirdjo, Prajudi, 1967
  - Alton, William H., 1969
  - American Field Service - students, 1965
  - American Foreign Service Association, 1962-1964
  - American Institute of Architects - Hawaii Chapter, 1968
  - American International School, 1965
  - American Legion Magazine, 1961
  - American Management Association, Inc., 1967
  - Amussen, Robert M., 1965
  - Ananda, Peter, 1969
  - Anderson, Benedict R. O'G., 1969-1970
  - Anderson, Helen S., 1971
  - Anderson, Jean, 1967
  - Anderson, Mr. and Mrs. J. F., 1966
  - Anderson, R. E., 1963-1967
  - Anderson, Robert, 1966
  - Andrews, David K., 1968
  - Andrews, John K., 1969
  - Andrews, Richard B., 1960
  - Andrews, Robert W., 1970-1971
  - Ankerman, Gerald, 1968-1969
  - Ann Arbor Press, 1968
  - Ansberry, Louise, 1965-1967
  - Anstruther, Mrs. Peter, 1968
  - Antara News Agency, 1967-1968
  - Arajanwalla, Mrs. Piloo K., 1970
  - Ardi, Toni, 1965-1968
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish, 1964
  - Armstrong, Kim, 1969
  - Arnold, H. H., Jr., 1963
  - Arnold, Paul, 1966
  - Aron, Glen M., 1972
  - Aronowitz, Leonard, 1965
  - Arrowsmith, D., 1969
  - Asia Society, 1970-1971
  - Asian Development Bank, 1966-1967
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1966
  - Atkinson, T. W., 1968
  - Authors Guild, Inc., 1971-1972
  - Ave, Joop, 1970
  - Ayres, Arthur, 1970
  - Azwar, T. A. H., 1964
  - Babbitt, Marcy, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - "Back Number" Wilkins, 1963
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1964-1971
  - Bade, Florence H., 1971
  - Bagdja, Doesnaedi, 1967
  - Bahr, Dr., 1963-1964
  - Bailey, Frank L., 1970
  - Baird, Matthew, 1965-1966
  - Baker, Edgar R., 1962
  - Baker, Elizabeth, undated
  - Baker, John C., 1967-1971
  - Baker, John M., 1967-1968
  - Baker, Russell, 1965
  - Baldwin, Charles F., 1968
  - Baldwin, Henry, 1967
  - Baldwin, I. L., 1971-1972
  - Balinong, Conchita, 1963
  - Ball, George W., 1964-1968
  - Bank of the Manhattan Co., 1949
  - Bannigan, John A., 1971
  - Barati, George, 1967
  - Barger, Herman H., 1964-1968
  - Barlow, Elizabeth G., 1971
  - Barnes, Rudolph C., 1968
  - Barnes, Lt. Gen., Verdi B., 1965
  - Barnett, Robert C., 1966
  - Barnett, Robert W., 1968-1971
  - Barrett, Edward W., 1965-1971
  - Barringer, Holda C., 1970
  - Bartlett, Thomas A., 1971
  - Bas, K. J., 1964
  - Basoeki, Col. R. Agoes, 1968-1969
  - Bates, Isabel, 1972
  - Battle, Lucius D., 1964-1965
  - Bauernschmidt, John, 1968
  - Baugh, Jerry P., 1959-1960
  - Bauman, Helen Wood, 1967
  - Beach, Gen. Dwight E., 1966
  - Beaver, Helen D., 1969
  - Bechtel, S. D., 1963-1964
  - Beckmann, George M., 1967
  - Beers, Howard W., 1965-1971
  - Bell, Bernard R., 1968
  - Bell, Eleanor, 1965-1967
  - Bell, James D., 1964-1971
  - Bellande-Signe, Suzanne, 1967-1969
  - Belmont, Alan H., 1972
  - Bennet, Augustus W., 1967
  - Benson, Brien, 1969-1972
  - Benson, George C., 1967-1970
  - Berding, Andrew H., 1960
  - Berg, Richard W., 1964
  - Berger, Samuel D., 1967
  - Bernard, Sir Dallas, 1970
  - Bernard, J. E., 1951
  - Bernice P. Bishop Museum, 1966
  - Bernstein, Bernard, 1963-1964
  - Bernstein, Richard, 1971
  - Biddle, Eric, 1965-1971
  - Bingham, Woodbridge, 1966
  - Bintara, B. P. H., 1964
  - Bitker, Mrs. Bruno V., 1971
  - Bitner, Harold M., 1968
  - Bixler, Julius S., 1966-1968
  - Black, Robert S., 1964-1969
  - Blackwelder, Justin, 1966
  - Blair, William McC., 1965-1966
  - Blaisdell, Thomas C., Jr., 1965-1966
  - Blodgett, Mr. and Mrs. Jerre R., 1972
  - Blok, Adele, 1968-1972
  - Blum, Dieter J., 1968-1969
  - Boelter, L. M. K., 1964-1966
  - Boeringer, Carl, 1968-1969
  - Boestaman, Soekondo, 1968
  - Boll, Carl R., 1969-1971
  - Bolling, Landrum R., 1971
  - Bolton, Bruce W., 1968
  - Bolton, Gertrude, 1971
  - Borel, Paul A., 1960
  - Borkin, Joseph, 1970
  - Bornet, Barbara, 1966-1967
  - Borton, Hugh, 1967
  - Boston University, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Bottoms, W. F., 1964
  - Bowie, Robert R., 1966
  - Bowles, Chester, 1963-1966
  - Boyer, Neil, 1969
  - Boyll, Jack R., 1971
  - Boynton, Stephen W., 1971
  - Braderman, Eugene, 1963
  - Bradley, Harry L., 1971
  - Bradley, Robert W., 1964
  - Bredin, J. Bruce, 1964-1971
  - Bredlow, Warren K., 1970
  - Breidster, Gen. Waldemar F., 1971
  - Brembeck, Cole S., 1965-1966
  - Brement, Marshall, 1961
  - Briggs, Patricia G., 1965-1966
  - Britton, O. O., 1971
  - Bronisch, G. P., 1965-1969
  - Brook, Thomas L., 1969-1972
  - Brooks, Lady, 1970
  - Brooks, Phillips, 1968
  - Broomfield, William S., 1967
  - Brotosoedjono, Wedo G., 1966
  - Brown, Arthur B., 1964
  - Brown, Edmund G., Sr., 1972
  - Brown, Foster S., 1966
  - Brown, Robert L., 1967
  - Brown, Winthrop G., 1964-1966
  - Brownell, John A., 1968
  - Bruce, Robert, 1968
  - Brunner, Gunter, 1965
  - Bryan, Thomas P., 1967
  - Buchanan, Wiley T., Jr., 1965
  - Buchi, Hans, 1968
  - Buck, David D., 1971
  - Buckmaster, Henrietta, 1968-1971
  - Budiardjo, Ali, 1968
  - Buffalo and Erie County Public Library, 1964
  - Buie, Thomasine K., 1967
  - Bulger, Paul G., 1964
  - Bundy, William P., 1964
  - Bunker, Ellsworth, 1965-1970
  - Bunnell, Frederick, 1965-1972
  - Burgess, David S., 1965
  - Burke, John W., Jr., 1960
  - Burke, Thomas J., 1964
  - Burling, Mrs. Edward B., 1966-1967
  - Burn, North, 1966
  - Burns, Deborah, 1966
  - Burns, John A., 1964-1968
  - Busching, Howard C., 1965
  - Bush, Monroe, 1965
  - Bushner, Rolland H., 1963-1970
  - Business Council, 1963
  - Businessmen's Information Center, 1968
  - Butcher, Charles, 1966-1967
  - Butts, R. Freeman, 1965
  - Byrd, Pratt, 1965
  - Cabot, Charles C., Jr., 1972
  - Cadagan, C. C., 1968
  - Cades, J. Russell, 1967
  - Calhoun, John A., 1966
  - Campbell, Bonham C., 1966-1967
  - Campbell, O. W., 1964-1966
  - Campbell, W. Glenn, 1967-1972
  - Campello, Robert, Jr., 1968-1971
  - Candlin, A. H. Stanton, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Cannon, Sherman, 1967-1969
  - Cantlon, C. E., 1969
  - Capella, Basil, 1966-1967
  - Cargo, William I., 1964
  - Carnadi, R., 1968
  - Carpenter, General John W., III, 1968
  - Carret, Philip L., 1968-1972
  - Carroll, Anne L., 1966-1967
  - Carter, Vincent M., 1965
  - Cate, Karl, 1964-1967
  - Celick, Lt. Col. A. J., 1969
  - Chadwick, Kathy, 1968
  - Champion, E. R., 1970
  - Chan, Wing-Tsit, 1966
  - Chandler, Alfred D., 1964-1971
  - Chandler, George, 1969-1971
  - Chang, Aida, 1968
  - Chang, Clarence F., 1968
  - Chang, Donald M., 1964-1965
  - Chaplin, George, 1966-1969
  - Charlotte-Mecklenburg Schools, 1965-1966
  - Chavan, Anant R., 1968
  - Chawner, Lowell J., 1968-1969
  - Chayes, Abram, 1964
  - Cheek, Debra S., 1966
  - Chen, King C., 1968
  - Chen, William, 1965
  - Cheng, David, 1967
  - Chennault, Anna, 1966
  - Chiang Ching-kuo, 1955
  - Chiang Kai-shek, Mme., 1955-1970
  - Chien Shin-liang, 1965
  - Childs, Richard S., 1944-1970
  - Ching, Hung-wo, 1966-1971
  - Chinn Ho, 1967
  - Chipman, Thelma, 1967
  - Cho, Sung Il, 1969
  - Choi, Wan Bok, 1965-1966
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1960
  - Chu, Hung-ti, 1967
  - Ciancimino, Frank E., 1971
  - Cisler, Walker L., 1966-1972
  - Citadel Publishing Co., 1964
  - Clark, Dale, 1968
  - Clark, T. C., Jr., 1965
  - Clark, William, Jr., 1971
  - Clegg, Mrs. C., 1968-1969
  - Cleveland, Harlan, 1969
  - Cleveland, R. G., 1968
  - Clough, Barbara M., 1964-1968
  - Clough, Meriam A., 1969
  - Coates, Byron C., 1969
  - Coates, Haskell, 1970
  - Coburn, Mary, 1971
  - Cochran, Katherine L., 1971
  - Cochrane, Willard W., 1965-1966
  - Coe, Bob, 1967
  - Coffin, L. H., 1964
  - Colbert, Vice Adm. R. G., 1971
  - Colby Junior College, 1970
  - Coleman, David S., 1967
  - Coleman, James J., 1968-1969
  - Colligan, Francis J., 1967
  - Collins, Gen. James F., 1963
  - Collins, Ray, 1966
  - Collins, Sumner, 1965
  - Colosimo, Mrs. Peter, 1964-1972
  - Columbia University, 1964-1967
  - Combs, Stanley L., 1968
  - Committee of Six, 1968-1969
  - Commonwealth Club of California, 1968
  - Conlan, Bill, 1971
  - Conlon, Dorothy, 1967
  - Conlon, Mr. and Mrs. Richard P., 1972
  - Connor, Frank H., 1970-1971
  - Conover, Harry, 1970
  - Conti, William, 1967
  - Continental Oil Company, 1967-1969
  - Cooley, George, 1966-1971
  - Coolidge, Harold J., 1964-1967
  - Cooper, A. Speight, 1971
  - Cooper, Ward, 1970
  - Cordier, Andrew W., 1965-1971
  - Cordiner, Ralph, 1960
  - Cornell University - Graduate School, 1967
  - Cornell University - Modern Indonesia Project, 1966-1969
  - Cosmos Club, 1965-1972 (Box 5)
  - Cottle, Sidney, 1971
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1965
  - Cousins, Norman, 1970-1972
  - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1965
  - Craig, Clayton B., 1966-1969
  - Crawford, Robert H., 1967
  - Crocker, Mrs. Stuart M., undated
  - Crockett, William J., 1966
  - Cronk, Edwin M., 1966
  - Cross, Charles T., 1970
  - Crum, Eleanor, undated
  - Crum, Frank, 1968
  - Cullen, Susan A., 1965
  - Culley, Perry, 1964
  - Cullman, Howard S., 1967
  - Cumming, Mr. and Mrs. Hugh S., Jr., 1971
  - Cupp, Donald E., 1971
  - Current, Inc., 1968
  - Cushing, R. L., 1968
  - Cutting, Windsor, 1965
  - Czayo, Mr. and Mrs. George M., 1964
  - Czyzak, John J., 1963-1964
  - Dagher, Sami, 1969
  - Dakan, Robert T., 1964-1968
  - Daly, Charles U., 1966-1971
  - Damon, G. Huntington, 1972
  - Dandison, Basil G., 1965
  - Danforth Foundation, 1970
  - Daniel, Lewis, 1964
  - Darling, Frank C., 1972
  - Da Silva, Jack, 1966
  - D'Auvray, J. V. Flor, 1965-1966
  - Davidson, Arthur D., 1965
  - Davies, Erica, 1971
  - Davis, Alton, 1971
  - Davis, Saville, n. d.
  - Davis, Spencer, 1969
  - Daycroft School, Inc., 1970-1971
  - Deamer, William C., 1964
  - DeBeausset, Mr. and Mrs. Val, 1967-1972
  - DeFranco, Leo, 1965-1966
  - DeGeer, Mr. and Mrs. Louis, 1966
  - De La Mare, Arthur, 1970
  - Delson, Robert, 1967
  - De Puy, Clifford, 1967
  - De Queljoe, David H., 1964-1969
  - Derachman, 1966
  - Desmond, Robert W., 1964-1970
  - Desmond, Thomas C., 1962
  - Development and Resources Corp., 1968
  - Dexter, John B., 1967
  - Dharma, Laksamana, 1969
  - Diah, B. M., 1967-1968
  - Dibble, Arnold, 1965
  - Dickinson, Mrs. William C., 1970
  - Diefenbach, Dale A., 1969
  - Dilliard, Irving, 1967-1970
  - Dilling, Mildred, 1966
  - Dillingham, Benjamin F., 1964-1965
  - Dillingham, Lowell S., undated
  - Djaafar, Hasan, 1963-1967
  - Djajadiningrat, Roswitha, 1967-1971
  - Djatikusumo, G. P. H., 1965
  - Djian, Tan Tek and Nora, 1966
  - Djojonegoro, Sukarno, 1967
  - Djuanda, 1958
  - Dodds, Dr. and Mrs. Harold W., 1966
  - Dodds, John W., 1969-1971
  - Domke, Paul C., 1964
  - Donohew, Jack N., 1968
  - Dorman, Dan E., 1965-1968
  - Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1965
  - Douds, Regina, 1966
  - Douglas, James, 1960
  - Douglas Oil Co., 1967
  - Douglas, William O., 1962-1970
  - Douglass, Inman H., 1970
  - Dowd, Harriet L., 1965
  - Drachkovitch, Milorad M., 1969
  - Draper, William H., Jr., 1966-1969
  - Driver, Thomas T., 1965
  - Drizari, Nelo, 1965-1969
  - Drummond, Roscoe, 1968-1972
  - Drummond, Roscoe and Geoffrey, 1969-1970
  - Drumright, Mr. and Mrs., 1965-1969
  - Drysdale, Peter, 1970
  - Duggan, William, 1965-1966
  - Duke, C. Martin, 1964
  - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing, 1969
  - Dumbros, Nicholas, 1967
  - Duncan, Sir Val, 1970
  - Dunne, F. P., Jr., 1964-1968
  - Durbrow, Elbridge, 1968
  - Durso, Leonard M., 1968-1969
  - East-West Center, University of Hawaii, 1964-1969 (Box 6)
  - Echols, John M., 1962-1966
  - Ecker-Racz, L. L., 1965-1971
  - Eckman, Arthur W., 1969-1972
  - Eddie, Scott M., 1968
  - Edin, Barbara, 1967
  - Eells, Richard, 1966
  - Egger, Rowland, 1962-1967
  - Ehrlichman, John D., 1972
    General note
    Photocopies in collection. Originals may be seen on request.
  - Eichelberger, Harold C., 1968
  - Eldridge, Donald A., 1966
  - Elegant, Robert, 1965
  - Elkins, Herbert M., 1969
  - Elliott, L. W., 1960
  - Ellis, Perry, 1965
  - Ellis, William A., 1964-1965
  - Emmerson, John K., 1972
  - Emmons, Arthur B., III, 1961
  - Engman, Charles A., 1965
  - Epton, Nina, 1964
  - Esposito, Vincent, 1966
  - Ethel, Col. Willis G., 1966-1967
  - Etherington, Mrs. Sanford G., 1965-1967
  - Evans, Glenn, 1970
  - Evans, Luther H., 1967
  - Everton, John Scott, 1965-1972
  - Ewell, Raymond, 1970
  - Ewing, Russell H., 1968
  - Fabik, R. Adm. T. J., 1965
  - Fahs, Charles B., 1967
  - Failing, Mrs. Clark, 1963
  - Falconi, Baron and Baroness Filipo, 1966-1970
  - Fales, Herbert P., 1966-1971
  - Fearey, Robert A., 1971
  - Federation of Japan Tuna Fishermen's Cooperative Association, 1967
  - Federspiel, Howard M., 1967
  - Feldman, George J., 1966
  - Felt, Adm. H. D., 1966
  - Feraru, Arthur, 1965
  - Fidel, E. Allen, 1960
  - Fifield, Russell H., 1962-1970
  - Fippin, William H., 1967
  - First Church of Christ, Scientist, 1964-1969
  - First National City Bank, Djakarta, Indonesia, 1967-1968
  - Fischer, Louis, 1964-1965
  - Fisher, Dorothy G., 1969
  - Flanagan, Mrs. Thomas, undated
  - Fleischman, Julius, 1966
  - Fleming, H. L., 1967
  - Fletcher, Richard R., 1964
  - Flinn, Daniel F., II, 1968
  - Flinn, Richard D., 1968-1970
  - Fogg, Ernest L., 1965
  - Foisie, Philip, 1971
  - Foley, Andrew J., 1971-1972
  - Folger, William, 1962
  - Follis, R. Gwin, 1963-1967
  - Ford, Clayton D., 1970-1972
  - Ford Foundation, 1967
  - Forster, J. Frank, 1966
  - Fox, Edwin L., 1964-1967
  - Franco, Napoleon, 1964
  - Franklin Book Programs, 1971
  - Fraser, Rodney, 1970
  - Frautshi, Mr. and Mrs. Walter, 1971
  - Freeman, Andrew A., 1962
  - Freeman, Fulton, 1971
  - Freeman, Orville, 1961
  - Freeman, W. Waldo, 1971
  - Freidus, Alberta, 1967
  - Frey, Mr. and Mrs. Richard C., 1970
  - Friend, Theodore W., III, 1967
  - Fujiyama, Naraichi, 1964
  - Furuuchi, Hiroo, 1966-1967
  - Gadbois, George H., Jr., 1966
  - Gaevernitz, Gero von, 1967-1969
  - Gainsbrugh, Martin R., 1967
  - Galbraith, Francis J., 1965-1972
  - Gale, Mary W., 1968-1971
  - Gallagher, Cornelius E., 1964
  - Gallman, Waldemar J., 1959-1960
  - Gallup, George, 1965
  - Gange, John, 1965-1966
  - Garinger, Joanne, 1967-1969
  - Garnett, Christopher, B., Jr., 1965 (Box 7)
  - Gautier, Kenneth F., 1964
  - Gaylor, Judith, 1965
  - Geist, John F., 1968
  - Gerbode, Mrs. Frank, 1966-1967
  - Gerson, Suzanne, 1968
  - Getchell, John S., 1969
  - Ghazali bin Shafie, 1969
  - Gibson, Weldon B., 1965-1969
  - Gilchrist, Andrew, 1966-1971
  - Gilliland, Nancy, 1968
  - Gilstrap, Sam, 1964-1971
  - Glassburner, Bruce, 1965-1968
  - Gleimius, Rudolf, 1966-1969
  - Goan, Mrs. The Eng., 1966
  - Goding, M. W., 1963
  - Goeshteim, Ilse, 1962
  - Goinga, Cornelius J., 1967
  - Gold, Vladimir, 1968
  - Goldberg, Harry, 1968-1969
  - Golden, Jack, 1965
  - Goldman, Anna F., 1963-1965
  - Goldstein, Ilse, 1965-1967
  - Golt, R. S., 1971
  - Goodfriend, Arthur, 1965-1970
  - Goodspeed, H. Kent, 1965-1966
  - Goransson, Tord, 1962
  - Gordon, S. C., 1969
  - Gornel, Daniel L., 1964-1966
  - Gostanian, E. L. Rose, 1968
  - Goto, Y. Baron, 1964-1965
  - Gould, Joseph S., 1965
  - Graebel, Gertrude, 1965-1968
  - Graham, Frank P., 1967
  - Grant, Robert Y., 1964-1966
  - Grauer, Ben, 1966
  - Graves, Judy, 1971
  - Graves, Thomas A., Jr., 1965
  - Gray, Jonathan, 1969
  - Green, George L., 1967-1968
  - Green, John, 1971
  - Green, Marshall, 1962-1970
  - Greenfield, James L., 1964
  - Gregorian, Arthur T., 1972
  - Groener, Mary E., 1964
  - Groth, Edward M., 1966
  - Gufler, Bernard A., 1960
  - Guggenheim, Harry F., 1965
  - Guild, Douglas S., 1965
  - Gulliksen, Gail J., 1969
  - Gullion, Edmund A., 1968-1971
  - Gunn, Edward K., 1966
  - Gurow, George, 1960-1970
  - Habberton, John, 1960
  - Habein, Harold C., 1970
  - Hadinoto, Nangkah, 1965
  - Hadinoto, Sujono, 1969
  - Hadji Halid, 1967
  - Hague, T. M., 1971
  - Hahn, Robert P., 1971
  - Haij, Lie Tong, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Haines, Harry C., 1965
  - Hall, Albert H., 1965
  - Hall, James J., 1964
  - Hall, Lloyd A., 1965
  - Hall, Theo E., 1968
  - Hallett, Mr. and Mrs. George H., Jr., 1966
  - Hamblin, F. N., 1968-1969
  - Hamengku Buwono IX, 1960-1965
  - Hamid, Annie, 1967
  - Hamilton, Thomas H., 1964-1967
  - Hammond, Mrs. David E., 1962-1970
  - Hamzah, Brig. Gen., 1967
  - Han, Ki Uk, 1968
  - Hanifah, Abu, 1968-1970
  - Hanna, Paul R., 1964-1972
  - Hannah, Norman B., 1964-1965
  - Hannon, Stuart L., 1966-1969
  - Hansen, Margaret, 1969
  - Harcourt, Brace, Jovanovich, Inc., 1965-1971
  - Hardi, Dr., 1969
  - Harding, R. N., 1964-1969
  - Harjono, 1967
  - Harker, Charles A., 1968
  - Harper, Robert W., 1965
  - Harrell, C. A., 1965
  - Harrelson, Mary, 1967
  - Harriman, W. Averell, 1963-1971
  - Harris, Elaine, 1970
  - Harris, Gen. Hunter, 1965
  - Harris, Michael, 1968
  - Harris, Mrs. William H., Jr., 1964-1966
  - Harrison, Tom, 1966
  - Hart, Sam, 1965
  - Harvard Club of Boston, 1972
  - Harvey, Barbara, 1968
  - Harvey, Col. William W., Jr., 1965-1967
  - Haryono, Joseph, 1970
  - Hasannuddin, Oteng, 1968
  - Hasibuan, Hadeli, 1969
  - Hassell, Arthur, 1966-1967
  - Hassler, Mrs. Russell H., 1970
  - Hastings, Edwin K., 1966
  - Hata, Samuel T., 1968
  - Hatta, Mohammad, 1964-1971
  - Hawaii - Department of Planning and Economic Development, 1966
  - Hawaii Island - Chamber of Commerce, 1965
  - Hawaii School for Girls, 1966
  - Hawkins, Mr. and Mrs. Everett Day, 1966-1971
  - Hayes, Samuel P., 1964-1970
  - Hays, Howard H., 1968
  - Hayward, Henry, 1971
  - Hayward, Adm. John T., 1968
  - Head, Simon, 1969
  - Hecht, Frank A., 1967-1969
  - Hedlund, John C., 1970
  - Heilpern, Bert, 1966-1967
  - Heinicke, Dr. and Mrs. Kurt, 1972
  - Helbig, Al, 1966
  - Heller, Walter W., 1971
  - Henderson, James E., 1960 (Box 9)
  - Henderson, John W., President, Washburn University of Topeka, 1968
  - Henderson, John W., State Department, 1960-1971
  - Henderson, Loy W., 1959-1961
  - Hengst, Marilyn, 1968
  - Henniker-Heaton, Peter J., 1969
  - Herman, Alexander C., 1960-1971
  - Herman, Pat, 1964-1967
  - Herman, Theodore, 1971-1972
  - Hersubeno, Mr. and Mrs. S. Sunarti, 1966-1970
  - Hertell, Hiram H., 1966-1971
  - Herter, Christian A., Jr., 1970
  - Hertz, Paul, 1955-1960
  - Hewitt, Mrs. Edwin S., 1967-1971
  - Hiatt, Robert, 1968
  - Hiemke, Hugo W., 1969
  - Hien, Tan Sing, 1967
  - Higgins, Benjamin, 1966
  - Higgins, Frank H., 1970-1971
  - Higgins, Mrs. Herbert N., 1964
  - Hiller, H., 1953
  - Hillhouse, A. M., 1965-1966
  - Hilsman, Roger, 1964-1970
  - Hind, Robert L., Jr., 1968
  - Hjermstad, Mrs. S. L., 1968
  - Ho, Sie Pek, 1966
  - Hobson, Jim, 1971
  - Hodge, Charles Lee, 1964
  - Hodges, Luther H., 1964-1972
  - Hohenberg, John, 1967-1971
  - Hohnen, Ross A., 1966
  - Holliday, George W., 1964
  - Hollowell, Fred S., 1946
  - Holmes, Julius C., 1963
  - Holmes, William J., 1965-1970
  - Holstein, Benjamin M., 1965
  - Honolulu Police Department, 1968
  - Honolulu Star-Bulletin, 1965
  - Hoover Institution, 1968
  - Hope, A. Guy, 1965
  - Hopkins, Frank S., 1969
  - Hopper, Richard H., 1964-1966
  - Horn, Robert C., III, 1967
  - Hornbeck, Stanley K., 1964-1965
  - Hornney, Lee, 1971
  - Horwitz, Robert, 1966